<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ludovic Rivallain</title><link>https://ludovic.rivallain.fr/</link><description>Recent content on Ludovic Rivallain</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ludovic.rivallain.fr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automation solutions for Cloud Provider</title><link>https://ludovic.rivallain.fr/posts/projects-examples/cloud-provider-automation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ludovic.rivallain.fr/posts/projects-examples/cloud-provider-automation/</guid><description>Think and build of multiple automation solutions for a Cloud Provider company:
Design and development of complex automation solutions to provide: additional customer self-service solutions (quota management, security services…) backend systems automation (automated backup policies, observability…) Multiple kind of automation services provided to end-users through: VMware Cloud Director + extensibility VMware vRealize Automation + extensibility Many other REST API endpoints Design of a new automation stack (K8s, FaaS, Argo workflow)</description></item><item><title>Storage as a Service for vCloud Director</title><link>https://ludovic.rivallain.fr/posts/projects-examples/storage-as-service-extension/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ludovic.rivallain.fr/posts/projects-examples/storage-as-service-extension/</guid><description>Think/Build/Run of a Storage-as-a-service extension for VMware vCloud Director:
Backend: vCD API extension: Multi-threaded Python service for automation orchestration Frontend: vCD UI extension: Angular-based UI published to tenants for self-service storage management Other technical concepts: Continuous-Integration pipeplines based on Gitlab CI, Swagger documentation of the REST API. Some vRO based automation for network provisioning</description></item><item><title>Hybridation of vRealize Automation</title><link>https://ludovic.rivallain.fr/posts/projects-examples/vra-hybridation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ludovic.rivallain.fr/posts/projects-examples/vra-hybridation/</guid><description>Hybridation of VMware vRealize Automation with a new public cloud provider:
Integration of a non-natively supported public cloud provider within vRA UI vRealize Orchestrator Dynamic Types, API integration, OpenStack Heat helpers.</description></item></channel></rss>